What's happening to me?
Where am I?
Where's Shido?
Where's Mio Takamiya?
Ahh, I'm sleepy...
No, I can't...
I have to...
I have to hurry back to Shido...
Will you sink?
Well, that works too.
Who's there?!
Who are you?!
My name?
I have none.
If I had to say, then I am you.
Me?
What on earth is going on here?
Is this a dream?
That's not correct,
but it's not far off either.
The only difference is we're inside
that woman, not your head.
That woman?
You mean Mio Takamiya?
Where's everyone else?!
If I'm here, then shouldn't
everyone else be here, too?
You're the only one alive in here.
All the others died as humans
when that woman stole their Sephirah.
Wait.
Died as humans?
What do you mean?
I know Origami and Kotori used to be human,
but Yoshino, Kaguya, Yuzuru,
and Natsumi are pure spirits like me, right?
No.
Aside from that woman,
all those known as Spirits
are just humans
who that woman granted Sephirah.
All of those you named just now
simply lost their memories
of when they were human.
Wha?!
All the Spirits used to be human?
No, I remember Nia
saying something like that, too...
But if that is true,
then why am I alive?
If I was a human too,
then I should've died as a human when my
Sephirah was stolen, just like the others!
I'll tell you.
That's because...
What I've just told you
is everything I understand.
Hmm?
I thought you would be confused,
but you've absorbed that surprisingly fast.
Yes.
No, I am confused.
But if what you say is true,
then right now I'm grateful for that.
Oh?
I'm still here and alive.
And if I'm alive,
then I can still fight back.
Your enemy is our mother.
Even if you are able to fight,
you're no match for her.
The most you can do is buy
a few minutes of time at best.
Then she'll eliminate you without
leaving a trace of consciousness.
I don't care.
If I buy a few minutes,
then Shido might be able to escape.
He might be able to think of some way
to break free of this situation.
That's enough hope to risk my life for.
Oh?
Though if you die,
then that means I will perish as well.
Since I am you.
I-Is that true?
Well, hmm...
Sorry.
But you want me to fight too, don't you?
Oh?
Why do you think that?
Because you called out to me, didn't you?
True!
Yes, that's true.
Then you should go, me.
Go fight to your heart's content.
Yes. Thank you, me.
Everyone's dead?
No way...
Shin...
I'm sorry.
I never wanted to make you sad,
but it'll be all right.
Those memories will be gone soon enough.
This sin is mine to bear alone.
So there's no need to blame yourself, Shin.
I...
We'll redo everything, starting from
that day you were shot in front of me.
Redo everything?
Forgetting everything?
Yes.
As Shinji Takamiya.
Shido!
You're safe?!
Tohka?!
Nothing is over yet!
Now, stand up, Shido!
Tohka!
I'm sorry, Tohka...
I...
For a moment, I nearly gave up...
What are you saying?!
Shido, you're still alive right now
because you didn't lose hope!
Could there be any better result than that?!
Thank you, Tohka.
Honestly, you keep saving me, Tohka.
I'm always relying on you too, Shido.
Even now, I was able to return because of you.
I'm able to stand before Mio because of you!
Tohka...
Yeah!
I see.
So it was you, Tohka.
Of course it is.
I was always sure that if
any would stand against me,
then it would be you.
I divided my power into ten Sephirah
and granted them to humans to create Spirits.
Though for some reason,
one of those ten Sephirah
sprouted its own consciousness.
Almost like the moment I was born, too.
Shin, you've realized it too, haven't you?
The difference between Tohka
and the other Spirits.
The one thing the other Spirits had
that Tohka didn't have.
A name.
Yes.
All the Spirits used to be human.
That's why they possessed
a name from the start.
However, Tohka was different.
Only Tohka and I were.
I had my share of confusion.
I had agonized over my lack of a name, too.
Though right now I'm grateful for that.
I was able to have you grant me my name
because I didn't have one of my own.
And I'm able to stand in front of you now
because I was never human!
This is throwing off my plans a bit,
but well, that's fine.
The result will still be the same.
I did it, Shido!
My attack went through!
Yeah.
Wait, it doesn't look like
it damaged her at all...
What are you saying?!
Until just now Halvanhelv didn't
even leave a scratch on her!
I see.
This seems a little troublesome.
My apologies, Tohka.
I'll take you seriously now.
I'll use my full might to steal Shin from you.
I won't let you!
Shido is mine!
Huh?
I see, so this...
I guess you stole a portion of my power
and the other Spirits' power
when you escaped from within me.
That's how you're able to use such power.
What?!
You are the only Pure Spirit
in existence aside from myself.
It means you're something like my counterpart.
So perhaps it's only natural that
you can do the same things I can.
Tohka!
I'll lend you power!
Yes, despair really doesn't suit you.
Tohka!
Sandalphon!
Halvanhelv, huh?
Ein Sof Ohr, Hennet.
Leitribish!
Well done, Tohka.
I'll have to respond to your
noble feelings and emotions.
Ein.
Tohka?
Tohka is no more.
Huh?
Ein, the Angel of nothingness,
ignores all logic and eliminates everything.
Tohka is no more.
She doesn't exist in this world.
I had no intention of using this Angel,
since it erases the Spirit Power that
Tohka possessed along with her, but...
I had no choice if I wanted
to be certain I put her down.
On the other hand, that also means
Tohka was pressuring me that badly.
So please give Tohka your praise.
Her feelings toward you were enough
for her to surpass her limits.
Now, Shin,
there truly are no others left to interfere.
The power I have now is plenty
to give you a body that never dies.
All that's left is restoring to you
to Shin completely.
Metatron!
Camael!
Zadkiel!
Gabriel!
Raphael!
Haniel!
Michael!
It's no use.
What's this?!
I'm sorry.
It's just difficult
when you fly around so much.
Now, Shin.
What?
It would seem I've made it in time.
Shido, well done staying alive for me.
Kurumi?!
What's going on?
I thought you were killed by Mio.
My apologies, Shido.
Honestly, I wanted to come
racing to your side sooner,
but it was quite the first for me,
so I couldn't get the feeling down right.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Yod Aleph, huh?
You're correct.
It's my eleventh bullet, one that
sends the target into the future.
I'm a clone of Kurumi Tokisaki
sent into the future from roughly
an hour ago using Yod Aleph.
Zaphkiel!
Yes, yes, I've been entrusted with this future.
I have been sent here
to kill you as your final assassin.
Are you being serious?
Do you think a mere clone can defeat me?
I can exist for as long as the Spirit Power
imbued in Yod Aleph lasts.
That's plenty of time to kill you!
Kurumi! What are you?!
I just told you, did I not?
I came to defeat Mio.
Oh, and one other thing.
I don't think I was able to forget
how your kiss felt, Shido.
Kurumi!
What a shame.
I wasn't enough.
Now everything is taken care of.
I applaud all of your feelings.
However, all of your resistance was futile.
Futile?
It wasn't futile.
Thanks to everyone...
and thanks to Tohka fighting for me,
Kurumi made it in time.
And Kurumi made me realize it.
Origami, Nia, Yoshino, Kotori, Mukuro,
Natsumi, Kaguya, Yuzuru, Miku, and Tohka...
None of their Angels
were able to work against you.
But I still have the power of one Angel left.
The power of an Angel
I've never once used before.
Kurumi sent her clone into the future
to make me realize that!
Zaphkiel!
Vav!
But what do I do?
What can I do to stop Mio's actions?
At this point in time,
Mio should already be inside of Kurumi.
If I'm not careful, she might
realize I'm trying to do something.
Shido?
What are you doing out here?
Tohka...
Wha?!
S-Shido?!
Tohka! Tohka!
Yes, it's me.
What's gotten into you, Shido?
Tohka, I...!
I had a dream.
A dream?
Yeah, a bad dream.
One where everyone was defeated
in the battle against DEM.
I couldn't do anything.
Even though you tried so hard for me, Tohka...
Shido...
It's all right.
I'm sure that won't happen.
Tohka...
Shido, you saved me.
I'm a Spirit,
and instead of calling me your enemy,
you reached out to me.
So I promise you.
No matter what happens,
I'll protect you, Shido.
Besides, you're the man who's
confronted me and the other Spirits.
Like we'd let DEM defeat us now.
I guess that's true.
What's the matter, Shido?
Thank you, Tohka.
Thanks to you, I think I see what I need to do.
I don't really understand,
but that's good then!
Reine.
Hmm?
What is it, Shin?
Reine,
would you go on a date with me tomorrow?
Episode 8
The One Who Pulled the Trigger
Episode 9 "A "Second" Date"
Shido has been granted one final chance.
But how can he conquer Reine and Mio?
Next time is Episode 9: A "Second" Date.
Return to the place in her memories once more.